{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"975/3",
			"answer":"975/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"963/3",
			"answer":"963/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"252/3",
			"answer":"252/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"180/9",
			"answer":"180/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"672/6",
			"answer":"672/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"166/2",
			"answer":"166/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"952/2",
			"answer":"952/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"540/2",
			"answer":"540/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"156/3",
			"answer":"156/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"90/5",
			"answer":"90/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}



		
	]
}